[{"answer": "We're constantly working at least a half a dozen or so investigations at both the Senate and the House.", "docId": "110420pmt", "aSentId": 3, "question": "Have you got any big scandals that you got up your sleeve for the next election campaign?", "qSentId": 2}, {"answer": "Much bigger than that.", "docId": "110420pmt", "aSentId": 23, "question": "Which would you take?", "qSentId": 22}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110420pmt", "aSentId": 29, "question": "Do you think so?", "qSentId": 28}, {"answer": "I think it's a great contribution.", "docId": "110420pmt", "aSentId": 31, "question": "You think that's your lifelong contribution?", "qSentId": 30}, {"answer": "Well, OK, let me try and give you a better one because I think it's a fascinating thing when you look at your career.", "docId": "110420pmt", "aSentId": 35, "question": "I said, my god, what greater compliment could they give me?", "qSentId": 34}, {"answer": "No, no, I don't have any regrets.", "docId": "110420pmt", "aSentId": 39, "question": "Here you are, you're super rich, you've had this amazing life, but part for me things, if you had your time again, could you be tempted into a totally different path?", "qSentId": 38}, {"answer": "Well, you pay a price for everything.", "docId": "110420pmt", "aSentId": 53, "question": "But what about for example the recent story of this pastor who came out with these outrageous comments -- mind you, outrageous because he made (INAUDIBLE) -- about wanting his right to burn the Quran and he then burns the Quran and as a result of that absolutely inevitably a lot of people get killed in Afghanistan?", "qSentId": 52}, {"answer": "I don't think you put any limits.", "docId": "110420pmt", "aSentId": 77, "question": "That there should never be any limits?", "qSentId": 76}, {"answer": "I feel good about being an American.", "docId": "110420pmt", "aSentId": 82, "question": "How do you feel about being an American right now?", "qSentId": 81}, {"answer": "I think I did see it coming.", "docId": "110420pmt", "aSentId": 88, "question": "Did you have any sense as a big businessman this was going to happen?", "qSentId": 87}, {"answer": "Well, I think morality is sometimes too subjective to define.", "docId": "110420pmt", "aSentId": 112, "question": "What would you say to that?", "qSentId": 111}, {"answer": "Hey, I put on my clothes the same way everybody else does every day.", "docId": "110420pmt", "aSentId": 122, "question": "I mean, where do your morals lie?", "qSentId": 121}, {"answer": "Hey, look, I'm the first guy to defend the philandering president.", "docId": "110420pmt", "aSentId": 127, "question": "What's your view, say, of sexual infidelity, for example?", "qSentId": 126}, {"answer": "That's big trouble.", "docId": "110420pmt", "aSentId": 132, "question": "That's big problems for you?", "qSentId": 131}, {"answer": "I think it's a tragedy the way the media exploited him.", "docId": "110420pmt", "aSentId": 141, "question": "You think people should leave him alone?", "qSentId": 140}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110420pmt", "aSentId": 146, "question": "You're a bipolar yourself, right?", "qSentId": 145}, {"answer": "Well, you know, the first sign is that you become euphoric, you know, about everything you do.", "docId": "110420pmt", "aSentId": 152, "question": "What is the sign for you that says he is?", "qSentId": 151}, {"answer": "Well, probably when I first started out.", "docId": "110420pmt", "aSentId": 171, "question": "When did you first think that?", "qSentId": 170}, {"answer": "Well, hypocrisy is terrible throughout our society.", "docId": "110420pmt", "aSentId": 185, "question": "Is there a lot of hypocrisy talked about the adult entertainment business, do you think?", "qSentId": 184}, {"answer": "What you see, must (INAUDIBLE) to you.", "docId": "110420pmt", "aSentId": 192, "question": "It's just the hypocrisy we're going after, you know?", "qSentId": 191}, {"answer": "That would be her business but we --", "docId": "110420pmt", "aSentId": 204, "question": "I mean, if you had a daughter that wanted to become a porn star, what would you have said to her?", "qSentId": 203}, {"answer": "Most of the time.", "docId": "110420pmt", "aSentId": 212, "question": "Is that always the case, Larry?", "qSentId": 211}, {"answer": "We do.", "docId": "110420pmt", "aSentId": 227, "question": "Isn't it up to you -- don't you have a slight moral responsibility to protect the more vulnerable girls who get hooked on this stuff?", "qSentId": 226}, {"answer": "Right.", "docId": "110420pmt", "aSentId": 236, "question": "Or are a classic repressed teenager before?", "qSentId": 235}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110420pmt", "aSentId": 239, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 238}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110420pmt", "aSentId": 242, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 241}, {"answer": "Yes, but got a few limitations on me.", "docId": "110420pmt", "aSentId": 249, "question": "I mean are you still as energized as you used to be, Larry?", "qSentId": 248}, {"answer": "Wow.", "docId": "110420pmt", "aSentId": 253, "question": "Who do you think has probably been more successful over the years, you or Hugh Hefner?", "qSentId": 252}, {"answer": "Think he's losing it.", "docId": "110420pmt", "aSentId": 255, "question": "Hefner is in his 80s now, you know?", "qSentId": 254}, {"answer": "First of all, when I said I was going to do this book, I reached out to my friend David Icenbach with -- from the university because he's a history professor.", "docId": "110420pmt", "aSentId": 271, "question": "What have you found from your study of president's sex lives?", "qSentId": 270}, {"answer": "Well, one thing that nobody knows, the youngest first lady was 19.", "docId": "110420pmt", "aSentId": 281, "question": "What were the most shocking discoveries, would you say?", "qSentId": 280}, {"answer": "It does (INAUDIBLE) between Warren Harding and John Kennedy.", "docId": "110420pmt", "aSentId": 288, "question": "Who was the most sexually promiscuous president, would you say?", "qSentId": 287}, {"answer": "That's probably true.", "docId": "110420pmt", "aSentId": 291, "question": "To you go along with that?", "qSentId": 290}, {"answer": "Yes, but see --", "docId": "110420pmt", "aSentId": 302, "question": "I mean, if you look at someone like Bill Clinton, for example, he's one of the most popular presidents ever, and yet he was a pretty naughty boy, wasn't he?", "qSentId": 301}, {"answer": "Every year, we're running an ad in the \"Washington Post\" that cost $85,000 to try to get as much dirt as we can on him.", "docId": "110420pmt", "aSentId": 311, "question": "Are you still investigating the sex lives of Republicans?", "qSentId": 310}, {"answer": "Well, we will expose anybody.", "docId": "110420pmt", "aSentId": 317, "question": "What makes you so confident that the Republicans that you're going to be exposing are any better or worse than Democratic rivals?", "qSentId": 316}, {"answer": "We're constantly working at least half a dozen or so investigation at both the Senate and the House.", "docId": "110420pmt", "aSentId": 338, "question": "Have you got any big scandals that you've got up your sleeve for the next election campaign?", "qSentId": 337}, {"answer": "I -- most of them are Republican.", "docId": "110420pmt", "aSentId": 342, "question": "So they'd all be Republicans, would they?", "qSentId": 341}, {"answer": "I wouldn't want to, but I would.", "docId": "110420pmt", "aSentId": 348, "question": "Well, what -- for arguments sake -- if you've got a story about President Obama, a sex scandal about him, would you feel it was right to publish that, given the obvious damage that would do to the country, and its reputation?", "qSentId": 347}, {"answer": "Because it would be very hypocritical of me not to.", "docId": "110420pmt", "aSentId": 350, "question": "You would?", "qSentId": 349}, {"answer": "I don't look at it.", "docId": "110420pmt", "aSentId": 359, "question": "What do you feel when you look back on what happened to you that day?", "qSentId": 358}, {"answer": "LYNT: I don't look at who shot me -- whoever it was shot me.", "docId": "110420pmt", "aSentId": 362, "question": "Do you feel bitter about it?", "qSentId": 361}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110420pmt", "aSentId": 367, "question": "It was an inter-racial photo shoot?", "qSentId": 366}, {"answer": "People always ask, \"What's it like being in that wheelchair?\"", "docId": "110420pmt", "aSentId": 371, "question": "Has it affected you in your spirit do you think?", "qSentId": 370}, {"answer": "I don't spend my life dwelling on anything I can't do nothing about.", "docId": "110420pmt", "aSentId": 375, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 374}, {"answer": "As someone who fought to expand the parameters of free speech in a very good way.", "docId": "110420pmt", "aSentId": 378, "question": "How would you like to be remembered?", "qSentId": 377}, {"answer": "I look at the redemption as being able to tell my story, to find my voice and try to make a change in the lives of others, and hopefully inspire them to come forward too.", "docId": "110420pmt", "aSentId": 395, "question": "How do you see where you've got to?", "qSentId": 394}, {"answer": "Till the age of 18.", "docId": "110420pmt", "aSentId": 411, "question": "And this went on for how long?", "qSentId": 410}, {"answer": "It varied.", "docId": "110420pmt", "aSentId": 413, "question": "And how often was this happening?", "qSentId": 412}, {"answer": "They divorced when I was 12 years old.", "docId": "110420pmt", "aSentId": 421, "question": "Where was your mother in all this?", "qSentId": 420}, {"answer": "Well, we didn't meet until our junior year.", "docId": "110420pmt", "aSentId": 443, "question": "Did you have even a tiny inkling about what might be happening?", "qSentId": 442}, {"answer": "Correct.", "docId": "110420pmt", "aSentId": 451, "question": "You only found out about the abuse after Stacey finally shot her father?", "qSentId": 450}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110420pmt", "aSentId": 474, "question": "Did you intend to kill him then?", "qSentId": 473}, {"answer": "The gun was downstairs.", "docId": "110420pmt", "aSentId": 482, "question": "What happens then?", "qSentId": 481}, {"answer": "And I shot him.", "docId": "110420pmt", "aSentId": 486, "question": "And you shot him?", "qSentId": 485}, {"answer": "He didn't realize he has been shot.", "docId": "110420pmt", "aSentId": 489, "question": "He does what -- how does he react?", "qSentId": 488}, {"answer": "I shot him a second time.", "docId": "110420pmt", "aSentId": 499, "question": "So what did you do?", "qSentId": 498}, {"answer": "I didn't know where it was.", "docId": "110420pmt", "aSentId": 501, "question": "In the head this time?", "qSentId": 500}, {"answer": "No, it's not that I wasn't allowed to.", "docId": "110420pmt", "aSentId": 507, "question": "You were told not to by your legal team?", "qSentId": 506}, {"answer": "I was 18 when I committed the crime and I was 20 when I finally went to trial.", "docId": "110420pmt", "aSentId": 513, "question": "You're how old now, 18, 19?", "qSentId": 512}, {"answer": "When they came back with guilty in the first degree, I knew that it would be life without parole.", "docId": "110420pmt", "aSentId": 515, "question": "And that moment when they say life with no parole, what are you thinking then?", "qSentId": 514}, {"answer": "Yes, yes.", "docId": "110420pmt", "aSentId": 520, "question": "Some people were claiming you killed him for his money?", "qSentId": 519}, {"answer": "Well, unfortunately when all this came out, I had already enlisted in the Navy.", "docId": "110420pmt", "aSentId": 523, "question": "Tom, let me just ask you, when this all comes out and the trial comes out, at what point does Stacey tell you about the abuse?", "qSentId": 522}, {"answer": "I always had hope, because I felt like when I went to trial, I made the right choice.", "docId": "110420pmt", "aSentId": 541, "question": "What was it like, prison for you, knowing perhaps there was never going to be any way out?", "qSentId": 540}, {"answer": "We filed a petition for clemency, not a pardon, not asking for full-out --", "docId": "110420pmt", "aSentId": 556, "question": "What happened?", "qSentId": 555}, {"answer": "Never.", "docId": "110420pmt", "aSentId": 558, "question": "You've never disputed killing your father?", "qSentId": 557}, {"answer": "Yes, he did.", "docId": "110420pmt", "aSentId": 574, "question": "And he believed you?", "qSentId": 573}, {"answer": "No, I do not.", "docId": "110420pmt", "aSentId": 584, "question": "Do you blame her for what happened?", "qSentId": 583}, {"answer": "Find your voice, tell.", "docId": "110420pmt", "aSentId": 589, "question": "What should they do?", "qSentId": 588}]